

131 TAIMOOR NAGAR, NEW FRIENDSCOLONY, MAHARANI BAGH, South Delhi, Delhi, 110025, India

■ vipinkumard365@gmail.com

**** 09871633867

NicestRudeGuy

ykd linkin

SKILLS

JavaScript React.js & Next.js 8

Node.js 7

7

WordPress

7

SQL 7 BootStrap & TailWind

CSS & SCSS

9

PHP

INTERESTS

Music Gaming

Photography Traveling

LANGUAGES

English Hindi 10 10

Vipin Kumar Dinkar

PM and Software Engineer

A Senior Software Engineer 4+ years of corporate and freelance experience. I have hired tech people to work with me. I've worked on MERN, LAMP & WORDPRESS Stacks over the years. I am IOT, Cloud & Block Chain enthusiast. Have worked on Open source projects like Brackets (Code Editor), rtMedia (WP Multimeda plugin with 20k+ active users), Gutenberg (blocks). Also got a chance to show my skills at Google's Projects AMP and WP WebStories.

WORK EXPERIENCE

 Accern
 (01/11/2021 - 06/01/2023)
 10up
 (01/06/2021 - 30/09/2021)

 Senior Front End
 Front Eng
 30/09/2021)

 Engineer
 Engineer

HTML5 SASS JavaScript React.js

HTML5 SASS JavaScript WordPress

(01/01/2017 -

01/12/2018)

WordPress Vip

Freelance

Developer

Web

https://10up.com/

JIRA Github HTML5 SASS Node.js JavaScript React.js

Accern.com

rtCamp (01/09/2020 - Front Eng 31/03/2021)

Engineer

HTML5 SASS JavaScript React.js

WordPress Vip

https://rtcamp.com/

Campk12 (01/06/2020 - 31/08/2020)

IS Teacher

EDUCATION

 USICT,GGSIPU
 (01/08/2017 - 01/08/2020)
 JIMS,VK
 (01/08/2014 - 01/08/2017)

 MCA(se), Software Engineering
 7.2
 BCA, Software Engineering
 01/08/2017)

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Covid Relief (01/04/2020 - 01/06/2020) Helper

REFERENCES

Gautam JhaFriend
Friend
Hitesh Aloney
Friend

SDE2 @ Brightly SDE4 @ Baazi Games

₹ 8802191242 **₹** 9870443933

■ gautamjha.mailbox@gmail.com ■ hiteshaloney75@gmail.com

Mehar Kaila Gaurav Kumar Singh

Friend Colleague
SDE2 @ Swiggy SDE3 @ Accern

\$\sqrt{9999771391} \$\sqrt{8143810766}

■ mehar0kaila@gmail.com